<Spase xmlns="http://www.spase-group.org/data/schema">
    <Version>2.2.2</Version>
    <NumericalData>
        <ResourceID>spase://VSPO/NumericalData/ISIS1/SFS/AveragedIonongrams</ResourceID>
        <ResourceHeader>
            <ResourceName>ISIS 1 Swept-/Fixed-Averaged Ionograms</ResourceName>
            <ReleaseDate>2012-04-11T10:42:31</ReleaseDate>
            <Description>This data set consists of ISIS 1 (International Satellites for Ionospheric Studies)ionograms that have been obtained through a data restoration project. The ISIS ionograms, consisting of a fixed-frequency and a swept-frequency part, were digitized from the original ISIS telemetry tapes. The digitized sounder data consisting of 8-bit receiver-amplitude values collected at a 40 kHz rate contain the time and the frequency associated with each sounder pulse. The frequency of each sounder pulse is determined from a 3rd degree interpolation between the times of the frequency markers as identified in the sounder video during the A/D operation. Included in this data set are the average-resolution ionograms (averages of each 4 successive 40 kHz 8-bit values) in CDF format. 

Software to read and display the individual CDF files is available at

ftp://nssdcftp.gsfc.nasa.gov/spacecraft_data/isis/software/

These CDF files were produced at NSSDC from the original PI-provided ionogram data. Other ionogram data sets available at NSSDC include the full resolution ionograms and average ionograms both in the PI-provided (OS2) binary format, ASCII header files with pass-specific information and the PCM data which contain header, time, AGC, frequency-marker information and telemetry-level data from all other ISIS instruments. The binary average ionograms and the ASCII header files are available online at

ftp://nssdcftp.gsfc.nasa.gov/spacecraft_data/isis/topside_sounder/

ISIS 1 and 2 data are available to the extent permitted by telemetry scheduling and the location of telemetry stations. A list of stations can be found at

http://nssdc.gsfc.nasa.gov/space/isis/isis-table1-new.html
and their location on a worldmap is shown in

http://nssdc.gsfc.nasa.gov/space/isis/isis_station_lar.GIF (</Description>
            <Contact>
                <PersonID>spase://SMWG/Person/Robert.F.Benson</PersonID>
                <Role>GeneralContact</Role>
            </Contact>
            <InformationURL>
                <Name>info about the digitization project</Name>
                <URL>http://nssdc.gsfc.nasa.gov/space/isis/isis-status.html</URL>
            </InformationURL>
            <PriorID>spase://VSPO/NumericalData/ISIS 1/SFS/AveragedIonongrams</PriorID>
        </ResourceHeader>
        <AccessInformation>
            <RepositoryID>spase://SMWG/Repository/NASA/GSFC/SPDF</RepositoryID>
            <Availability>Online</Availability>
            <AccessRights>Open</AccessRights>
            <AccessURL>
                <Name>Data from NSSDCFTP</Name>
                <URL>ftp://nssdcftp.gsfc.nasa.gov/spacecraft_data/isis/topside_sounder/</URL>
                <Description>Data from multiple telemetry stations</Description>
            </AccessURL>
            <AccessURL>
                <Name>CDAWeb FTP area</Name>
                <URL>ftp://cdaweb.gsfc.nasa.gov/pub/istp/isis1/all/</URL>
                <Description>FTP repository of ISIS-1 Topside sounder ionograms from multiple telemetry stations</Description>
            </AccessURL>
            <AccessURL>
                <Name>CDAWeb HTTP area</Name>
                <URL>http://cdaweb.gsfc.nasa.gov/sp_phys/data/isis1/all/</URL>
                <Description>HTTP repository of ISIS-1 Topside sounder ionograms from multiple telemetry stations</Description>
            </AccessURL>
            <AccessURL>
                <Name>CDAWeb</Name>
                <URL>http://cdaweb.gsfc.nasa.gov/sp_phys/</URL>
                <Description>ISIS 1 ionograms data with subset, plot, list functionalities from CDAWeb</Description>
            </AccessURL>
            <Format>CDF</Format>
        </AccessInformation>
        <InstrumentID>spase://SMWG/Instrument/ISIS1/SFS</InstrumentID>
        <MeasurementType>Waves.Active</MeasurementType>
        <TemporalDescription>
            <TimeSpan>
                <StartDate>1969-01-30T14:50:12</StartDate>
                <StopDate>1983-12-30T15:19:33</StopDate>
            </TimeSpan>
        </TemporalDescription>
        <ObservedRegion>Earth.NearSurface.Ionosphere</ObservedRegion>
    </NumericalData>
</Spase>